There's one more report I would like to explore in a bit more detail.
还有一个我想更详细地探讨的报告
But first, let me tell you a story.
但首先 我来给你讲一个故事
A while back I was consulting for a large and successful lifestyle website.
前一段时间 我正在为一个大型的、成功的生活方式方面的网站做咨询
They were ready to redesign their website and they wanted some help.
他们准备重新设计他们的网站 并且想要一些帮助
I sat down with one of their main salespeople.
我和他们的一位主要销售人员坐在一起
He told me they had made a few decisions already.
他告诉我他们已经做了几个决定
There was an area of the website with lots of pictures sent in
该网站有一个区域 里面有大量的
by users of the site where they showcased their remodel.
网站用户发送的照片 在那里他们展示了他们的改造情况
Now the sales guy did not like this part of the site at all
现在销售人员根本不喜欢该网站的这一部分
because it was incredibly hard to sell advertising for this section.
因为这个部分的广告销售非常困难
None of the big appliance brands that he talked to,
他协商过的大家电品牌
wanted to have their ads appear next to someone's new but not so great looking kitchen.
都不想把他们的广告展示在别人的看起来并不怎么样的新厨房旁边
So they decided this area had to go.
所以 他们决定必须去掉这个部分
Now when we dug into Google Analytics,
现在 当我们深入钻研 Google Analytics 时发现
it became clear that this pre-post remodeling content was very popular with users.
很明显 这个前期改造内容很受用户欢迎
They were some of the most visited pages and these pages were engaging,
是访问量最大的页面之一 而且参与度很高
low bounce rates, long time spent, et cetera.
跳出率很低、花费时间长等等
But what was more,
但更重要的是
when we looked at the page flow,
当我们查看页面流时
we noticed that in many cases
我们注意到在很多情况下
the second interaction was with content in the designer section,
他们的第二个互动是与设计师部分的内容互动
where designers were showcasing their remodels.
在那里 设计师们正在展示他们的改造情况
Of course this area was way more slick and very popular among advertisers.
当然 这个区域在广告客户中更为灵活和受欢迎
So I sat down again with a salesperson and I told
因此 我又和一位销售人员坐了下来 并且告诉他
him I thought the user-generated content should stay.
我认为用户生成的内容应该保留下来
These were pages that inspired users to check out some of the designer's pages.
这些页面激发了用户来查看设计师的一些页面
And instead of making them disappear,
因而不能让它们消失
we should promote them, make them more prominent and easy to find.
我们应该提升它们 让它们更加突出并容易找到
But I also told him that he should not be worried about pushing them in a sales call.
但我也告诉他 他不应该担心在销售电话中推销它们
He should use them as a traffic driver to
他应该把它们作为流量推动力
the areas that mattered more to him and to his clients,
用于对他和他的客户来说更重要的地方
the designer showcase pages.
即 设计师展示页面
And so the user-generated content pages were saved and they drove
因此 用户生成的内容页面被保存下来
an increasing amount of traffic to the areas that paid off for the company.
并且驱使越来越多的流量进入为公司付费的区域
So which report in Google Analytics helped me to figure this out?
那么 Google Analytics 中的哪个报告帮助我了解了这一点？
The behavior flow report,
行为报告部分中的行为流程报告
in the behavior reports section helps to get
有助于了解人们
a view on how people flow from one page to the
如何从一个页面流向
next and what the role is of a page in flowing
另一个页面 以及一个页面在流量流向其它重要页面中的角色
traffic to other important pages. Let's take a look.
让我们来看一看